<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ARTICLE>
  <HEADING>ABOUT</HEADING>
  <CONTENT>
    <![CDATA[
They go by many names, many know them as the Sky Drifters, Drifters for short. <br>
The world is both a cruel and beatiful one yet it doesn’t phase them. <br>
This faction of sky citizens doesn’t aim to rule with an Iron Fleet, nor be ruled by one; for they only kneel to one master, the Winds themselves.
<br><br>
The Drifters are often spread far and wide, but you’ll easily spot them soaring across the skies like they were forged in their wake. In fact their leader, a young gentlemen that goes by the name of Dayox, can often be spotted away from the main pack, crashing through the wind on his signature skimmer-class ship, The Swift. What it lacks in size, it certainly makes up for in agility; the ship I mean.
<br><br>
While the Drifters aren’t the warring type, they are always prepared to answer a call to arms. Yet this does not mean they are hostile to those that approach them, in fact you’ll fine they’re more than happy to lend a hand to those that require it.
<br><br>
When travelling long distances, many Drifters adopt more larger and bulkier Trawler-class vessels, towing any smaller ship behind them. This could not be more true for the Phoenix, a large Trawler and cargo vessel often carrying it’s captain to distant skies.
<br><br>
If the Drifters intrigue you, then do not hesitate to approach them, they’re always looking to for members, just ask for Dayox and he’s often on hand to welcome new citizens to the ranks.
<br><br>
For they are The Sky Drifters, children of the skies, followers of the winds, weavers of fate.
<br><br>
———————————————————————————————————————————————————————————
<br><br>
Basic Information about us:
<br><br>
We are one of the oldest factions of Worlds Adrift, being one of a few Precursor factions; a faction that was founded before the Alliance Integration on the Website. We’re also pretty big if I do say so myself with I believe 50 members under the name of Sky Drifter.
<br><br>
We occasionally host Social Nights where we jump onto a skype call, discuss WA news, play games and generally have a good time!
<br><br>
The Sky Drifters are not your typical faction, we all do our own thing in a sense, all pursue our own goals while helping out each other whenever we can. The Sky Drifters are more of a group of individuals that fly under one banner, we aim to bring about harmony to WA, help those that need it and make the world as pleasant as possible.
<br><br>
We have a Sister Faction, WANMED who focus on being our more combat ready ships and crews, often being the Vanguard of the fleet, led by Captain @ryouji .
<br><br>
Currently we are allied with a few other factions, mostly those that harbour the same beliefs as ourselves.
<br><br>
In terms of faction relations and communications check here for reference. , any faction that is listed under ‘Ally’ is on limits to communicate with. Naturally ‘Enemy’ are banned factions in terms off communication following incidents that occurred previously. ‘Neutral’ are also unavailable for communication as negotiations are in order and I don’t want transferal of information between potential Enemies. Generally no information should be shared with other factions ally or not.
<br><br>
I think the most important thing to know about us is we are just trying to have some fun and help people out as we do it, so if we seem like the group for you, by all means ask as many questions as possible and get involved!
<br><br>
Good luck out there!
<br><br>
Dayox, Chief of the Sky Drifters
]]>
  </CONTENT>
</ARTICLE>
